<resources>
    <string name="app_name">B-Active</string>
    <string name="ex1">1- Start in a press-up position with your hands shoulder-width apart directly beneath your shoulders.\n\n2- As quickly as you can, pull your right knee towards your chest without letting it touch the floor then return to the start position.\n\n3- Repeat step 2 with your left leg.\n\n4- Continue until you have completed the required amount of reps.</string>
    <string name="ex2">1- Start in a standing position with arms by your sides. Engage the core slightly and set the shoulders, ready for movement.\n\n2- Keeping arms and legs straight (but not locked out) simultaneously jump the legs out to the sides and raise the arms to shoulder height.\n\n3- Stabilise the hips, core and shoulder girdle.\n\n4- Return to start and continue at a controlled rhythmic pace for time or reps.</string>
    <string name="ex3">1- Stand straight with feet hip-width apart.\n\n2- Tighten your stomach muscles.\n\n3- Lower down, as if sitting in an invisible chair.\n\n4- Straighten your legs to lift back up.\n\n5- Repeat the movement.</string>
    <string name="ex4">1- Get down on all fours, placing your hands slightly wider than your shoulders.\n\n2- Straighten your arms and legs.\n\n3- Lower your body until your chest nearly touches the floor.\n\n4- Pause, then push yourself back up.\n\n5- Repeat.</string>
    <string name="ex5">1- Stand with your feet hip-width apart.\n\n2- Step forward and bend both knees, lowering until your knees are bent at a 90-degree angle.\n\n3- Shift forward onto the lead leg.\n\n4- Push off on both legs and step through, lifting your back leg and bringing it forward so your rear foot lands ahead of you in a lunge position.</string>
    <string name="ex6">1- Lie on your back with your feet flat on the floor, hip-width apart.\n\n2- Breathe out, squeeze your abs and lift your head, neck and shoulders up toward the ceiling.\n\n3- Breathe in and return to the starting position.</string>
    <string name="ex7">1- Start in a press-up position.\n\n2- Bend your elbows until your forearms are on the floor beneath your shoulders so your body is in a straight line from your feet to your head.\n\n3 -Keep your abs tight and look at the space between your hands to ensure a neutral spine position.\n\n4- Hold the position for as long as you can.</string>
    <string name="ex8">1- Stand with your feet shoulder-width apart and your arms by your sides.\n\n2- Lower into a squat position and place your hands on the floor.\n\n3- Kick or step your legs back into a plank position.\n\n4- Jump or step your legs forward to return to a squat position.\n\n5- Return to the standing position.</string>
    <string name="ex9">1- Stand with your feet hip-width apart.\n\n2- Lift up your left knee to your chest.\n\n3- Switch to lift your right knee to your chest. Continue the movement, alternating legs and moving at a sprinting or running pace.</string>
    <string name="ex10">1- Lie on your back with your arms down by your sides.\n\n2- Lift both of your legs a few inches off the ground and separate them slightly into a “V” shape. Engage your core and press your lower back into the floor.\n\n3- Keeping both legs straight, bring your legs together and cross your right leg over the left. Widen your legs into a “V” again, and then bring your legs together again, this time crossing your left leg over the right.\n\n4 -Continue alternating until you’ve completed all reps.</string>

    <string-array name="array_months">
        <item>Jan</item>
        <item>Feb</item>
        <item>Mar</item>
        <item>Apr</item>
        <item>May</item>
        <item>Jun</item>
        <item>Jul</item>
        <item>Aug</item>
        <item>Sep</item>
        <item>Oct</item>
        <item>Nov</item>
        <item>Dec</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="january">January</string>
    <string name="february">February</string>
    <string name="march">March</string>
    <string name="april">April</string>
    <string name="may">May</string>
    <string name="june">June</string>
    <string name="july">July</string>
    <string name="august">August</string>
    <string name="september">September</string>
    <string name="october">October</string>
    <string name="november">November</string>
    <string name="december">December</string>


    <string-array name="array_measurements">
        <item>Metric</item>
        <item>Imperial</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="array_activity_levels">
        <item>Little to no exercise</item>
        <item>Light exercise (1–3 days per week)</item>
        <item>Moderate exercise (3–5 days per week)</item>
        <item>Intensive exercise (6–7 days per week)</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="array_weekly_goals">
        <item>loose weight</item>
        <item>gain weight</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="array_weekly_goals_kg">
        <item>0.5</item>
        <item>1</item>
        <item>1.5</item>
    </string-array>


</resources>